# YAML configuration file for questions in gcm_setup.py
# 
# You must adhere to the following question structure:
#   - name:       'Question name' 
#     type:       'text'                              or 
#                 'select'                            or 
#                 'confirm'                           or 
#                 'path'
#     prompt:     'Prompt shown to user'
#     default:    'Default option text for question'  or
#                  True/False                         (if type == confirm) or 
#                 'runtime'                          (if default determined at runtime)
#     options:    
#                 'Option 1 text'   : 'Option 1 value'
#                 'Option 2 text'   :  'Option 2 value'
#     followup:   
#                 name        : 'name of followup question'
#                 conditions  : (dict of equality conditions for followup)
#                                   ans     : ''
#     callback:   'name of callback function'
#
# Fields will be ignored if they do not apply to question type.

mainquestions: 
# Experiment ID
  - name:     'expid' 
    type:     'text'
    prompt:   'Enter the Experiment ID:'
    default:  '0'
    options:
    followup:
    callback: 

# Experiment description
  - name:     'expdesc'
    type:     'text'
    prompt:   'Enter a 1-line Experiment Description:'
    default: 
    options:
    followup:
    callback: 

# Clone old experiment
  - name:     'cloneexp'
    type:     'confirm'
    prompt:   'Do you wish to CLONE an old experiment?'
    default:  False
    options:
    followup: 'cloneparams'
    callback: 

# Horizontal atmospheric resolution
  - name:     'hrcode'
    type:     'select'
    prompt:   'Select the Atmospheric Model Horizontal Resolution Code:'
    default:  
    options:   
              'Cubed Sphere:   c12  --  8   deg'          :  12
              '                c24  --  4   deg'          :  24
              '                c48  --  2   deg'          :  48
              '                c90  --  1   deg'          :  90
              '                c180 -- 1/2  deg (56-km)'  :  180
              '                c360 -- 1/4  deg (28-km)'  :  360
              '                c720 -- 1/8  deg (14-km)'  :  720
              '                c1440 - 1/16 deg ( 7-km)'  :  1440
              'DYAMOND Grids:  c768 -- 1/8  deg (12-km)'  :  768
              '                c1536 - 1/16 deg ( 6-km)'  :  1536
              '                c3072 - 1/32 deg ( 3-km)'  :  3072
    followup:
    callback: 

# Vertical atmospheric resolution
  - name:     'agcmlm'
    type:     'select'
    prompt:   'Select the Atmospheric Model Vertical Resolution Code:'
    default:  'L72'
    options:  
      'L71'  : 71
      'L72'  : 72
      'L91'  : 91
      'L127' : 127
      'L132' : 132
      'L137' : 137
      'L181' : 181
    followup: 
#     callback: 

# # Atmospheric microphysics
#   - name:     'agcmpmp'
#     type:     'select'
#     prompt:   'Select the Atmospheric Model Microphysics Option:'
#     default:  '1MOM  --  3-phase 1-moment Bacmeister et al'
#     options:  
#       '1MOM  --  3-phase 1-moment Bacmeister et al'                       : '1MOM'
#       'GFDL  --  6-phase 1-moment Geophysical Fluid Dynamics Laboratory'  : 'GFDL'
#       'MG1   --  3-phase 2-moment Morrison & Gettleman'                   : 'MG1'
#     followup: 
#     callback: 


# # Hydrostatic atmosphere
#   - name:     'usehydro'
#     type:     'confirm'
#     prompt:   'Use Hydrostatic Atmosphere?'
#     options:  
#     # TODO: REPLACE 
#     # default:  !!bool @CFG_HYDROSTATIC@ # Force CMAKE variable to be treated as bool
#     default:  !!bool False
#     followup: 
#     callback: 

# # ioserver
#   - name:     'useioserver'
#     type:     'confirm'
#     prompt:   'Use IOSERVER?'
#     options:  
#     default:  'runtime'
#     followup: 
#     callback: 

# # processor model
#   - name:     'procmodel'
#     type:     'select'
#     prompt:   'Select the Processor Model you wish to run on:'
#     options:  
#               'Haswell'         : 'hasw'
#               'Skylake'         : 'sky'
#               'Cascade Lake'    : 'cas'
#     default:  'Skylake'
#     followup: 
#     callback: 

# # followupquestions:

